{
  "students": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "username": "Ali",
      "email": "Ali@gmail.com",
      "password": 123
    },
    {
      "email": "Salma@gmail.com",
      "userName": "Salma",
      "password": "12345",
      "id": 3
    },
    {
      "email": "Salwa@gmail.com",
      "username": "Salwa",
      "password": "12345",
      "id": 8
    },
    {
      "email": "yasser@gmail",
      "username": "Yasser",
      "password": "12345",
      "id": 9
    },
    {
      "email": "Salmaa@gamil",
      "username": "Samiaa",
      "password": "12345",
      "id": 10
    },
    {
      "email": "Asmaa@gmail.com",
      "username": "Asmaa",
      "password": "12345",
      "id": 11
    }
  ],
  "Doctor": [
    {
      "username": "admin",
      "email": "admin@admin.com",
      "password": 123,
      "id": 1
    }
  ],
  "Subjects": [
    {
      "name": "Math"
    }
  ],
  "login": [
    {
      "username": "Salwa",
      "role": "student",
      "id": 1
    }
  ],
  "questions": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "question": "2+2",
      "answer1": "2",
      "answer2": "1",
      "answer3": "3",
      "answer4": "4",
      "correctAnswer": "4"
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "question": "2*2",
      "answer1": "2",
      "answer2": "1",
      "answer3": "3",
      "answer4": "4",
      "correctAnswer": "4"
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "question": "2*3",
      "answer1": "6",
      "answer2": "1",
      "answer3": "3",
      "answer4": "4",
      "correctAnswer": "6"
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "question": "2*5",
      "answer1": "10",
      "answer2": "1",
      "answer3": "3",
      "answer4": "4",
      "correctAnswer": "10"
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "question": "2-1",
      "answer1": "2",
      "answer2": "1",
      "answer3": "3",
      "answer4": "4",
      "correctAnswer": "1"
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "question": "2+2",
      "answer1": "2",
      "answer2": "1",
      "answer3": "3",
      "answer4": "4",
      "correctAnswer": "4"
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "question": "2*2",
      "answer1": "2",
      "answer2": "1",
      "answer3": "3",
      "answer4": "4",
      "correctAnswer": "4"
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "question": "2*3",
      "answer1": "6",
      "answer2": "1",
      "answer3": "3",
      "answer4": "4",
      "correctAnswer": "6"
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "question": "2*5",
      "answer1": "10",
      "answer2": "1",
      "answer3": "3",
      "answer4": "4",
      "correctAnswer": "10"
    },
    {
      "id": 10,
      "question": "2-1",
      "answer1": "2",
      "answer2": "1",
      "answer3": "3",
      "answer4": "4",
      "correctAnswer": "1"
    }
  ],
  "Score": [
    {
      "score": 4,
      "id": 1
    }
  ],
  "contact": [
    {
      "id": 1
    }
  ]
}